好了 我们要出门了... 回见
Okay, we're headed out... See you later.
先别走
Before you leave,
能帮我一起测试下抗噪耳机的功效吗?
could you test these noise-cancelling headphones?
当然没问题
Yeah, sure.
好
Okay.
开始
Go ahead.
嘿 能听见我说话吗?
Hello, can you hear me?
Sheldon 其实我已经有两年没有
Sheldon, I haven't changed the filter
给滤水壶换过滤器了
in the water pitcher in two years.
Bernadette给你起了个绰号叫"纯真可乐达"(一种无酒精果汁)
Uh, Bernadette's nickname for you is the virgin pina colada.
你那张乔治・卢卡斯（著名导演）的亲笔签名其实是我伪造的
Your George Lucas autograph is really a “me” autograph.
好吧 事实上有一次我懒得走路
Yeah, well, once I was too lazy to walk across the hall,
就直接用了你的牙刷了
so I used your toothbrush.
还有一次你在睡着了的时候
Ooh, and one time when you were asleep,
Amy完全脱光了...
Amy totally took off her...
所以你是我心中的最佳室友
And that's why you're the best roommate ever.
真遗憾我没听到前面的部分
Now I'm sad I didn't hear it.
你要那副耳机干嘛?
So what do you need the headphones for?
我已经努力了数月
Well, I've been struggling for months
来想出一个不会使质子衰变的
to come up with a theory of dark matter
暗物质理论
that doesn't make protons decay.
我希望通过改善自己的工作环境
I'm hoping to finally tackle it
来搞定它
by optimizing my work environment.
瞧 我已经让我的茶水处在最佳饮用温度了
See, I've got, uh, my tea is at the perfect sipping temperature.
我还买了绒布四角裤
Uh, I have fleece-lined boxer shorts
让我的小屁屁更加地温暖舒适
to keep my tushie toasty.
还有 最后还有这张
And then, oh, last but not least,
鼓舞人心的猫咪海报
this inspirational cat poster,
我在上面ps了物理学家理查德・费曼
improved with the reassuring face
那张可靠的脸蛋儿
of physics renegade Richard Feynman.
(坚持住)
这就是昨晚他非要你带他去"办公室用品店"的原因?
Is that why you had to take him to Office Depot last night?
我不想谈那件事了
I don't want to talk about it
我们走了 这就是你的天下了
There, the place is all yours.
恩 玩的开心哦
Yeah, have fun.
我会的 没有什么能比
Oh, I will... nothing more fun
研究能改写历史的科学理论更好玩的了
than a paradigm-shifting evening of science.
你就知道洗澡时给我涂肥皂
And you thought it was soaping me up in the shower.
拜拜
Bye.
好
Okay.
开工了
Here we go.
质子衰变
Proton decay.
嘿 我们回来了
Hey, we're home.
有任何进展了吗?
Any progress?
就你们这样不断地打扰
How could there be?
人家怎么可能有进展?
With these constant interruptions.
我爱他 但是如果他坏了 我们也还是别换新的
I love him, but if he's broken, let's not get a new one.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
*  自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall * * We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第八季十三集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 凤梨酥
翻译: 爱喝牛奶 猫呗 上等五仁儿 leochh
校对: UU2222222了
你在干啥呢?
What are you doing?
该出发了
It's time to go.
我今天不去上班了
I'm not going to work today.
你想知道为什么吗?
And would you like to know why?
因为 你花了整晚研究暗物质
Ah, you're upset because you spent the whole night working
却没有找到一个突破点 心情很郁闷了
on dark matter and didn't make a breakthrough,
然后现在你又觉得自己更换研究领域是个大错误
and now you're worried you made a huge mistake switching fields,
所以你就打算闷闷不乐地坐一整天?
and you're gonna sit around and sulk all day?
像个大婴儿一样
Like a big old baby.
如果有需要 打电话给我
Call me if you need anything.
我已经宅在屋里好久了
I've been cooped up in here too long.
也许呼吸下新鲜空气会好点
Maybe I need some fresh air.
Penny啊?
Penny?
额 怎么了?
Ugh, what?
你听上去很痛苦的样子
You sounded in distress.
我还以为你遭遇了什么不幸
I was worried something unpleasant was happening to you.
比如说 谋杀
Like a murder.
或者是在和leonard啪啪啪呢
Or spontaneous coitus with Leonard.
哦 我只是在做烦人的运动
Oh, I'm just doing this awful workout.
我讨厌它
I hate it.
恩 那既然你讨厌它 为什么还要做呢?
Well, if you hate it, then why are you doing it?
不过这个问题放在
Although I could ask the same question
你和leonard的啪啪啪的事儿上也可以
about coitus with Leonard.
我不知道... 我想我只是喜欢这种讨厌的感觉
I don't know... I guess I like that I hate it.
它让我更加努力
It makes me work harder.
澄清一下...
And to clarify...
我说的是运动 Sheldon
The exercise, Sheldon.
你不去收拾下去上班吗?
Shouldn't you be getting ready for work?
我今天不去了
I'm not going.
你想知道原因吗?
Would you like to know why?
原因是你因为昨晚没有任何进展而难过了
Uh, you're sad about not getting anything done last night,
所以你打算今天呆坐着自己生气?
so you're gonna sit around and pout about it?
看来我没有自己以为的那么神秘
Boy, I'm not nearly as mysterious as I think I am.
我发明了一个游戏
I invented a game.
- 你想玩吗?  - 当然
- You want to play?  - Sure.
这个游戏叫做"是Emily还是Cinnamon"
It's called "Emily or Cinnamon"
我告诉你一些Raj说的话 你来猜猜
I give you actual quotes I've heard Raj say,
这些话他是对他女朋友说的还是对他的狗狗说的
and you guess if he was talking to his girlfriend or his dog.
开始吧 尽情嘲笑我
Go ahead, make fun.
你不会让我丢脸的
You can't embarrass.
我已经有了一个漂亮的女友了
I've got a beautiful girlfriend
还有了一只爱我爱到会喝我洗澡水的狗狗
and a dog who loves me so much she drinks my bathwater.
好了 下面这句话他是对Emily还是Cinnamon说的:
Okay, who was he talking to, Emily or Cinnamon:
"要知道 你不在床上时
"I want you to know, the bed feels so lonely
我真是寂寞如雪"
when you're not in it."
这游戏的发展我不太喜欢
I may not be liking this game so much.
是Cinnamon 再来
Cinnamon. Give me another one.
好 Emily还是Cinnamon:
Okay, Emily or Cinnamon:
"快看快看 我给咱们买了情侣毛衣!"
"Check it out, I got us matching sweaters!"
我们都收到那张圣诞贺卡了... 是Cinnamon
We all got the Christmas card... Cinnamon.
男人可以同时宠爱一个女人和一只宠物
You know, a man can care deeply about a woman and a pet.
这又不奇怪
It's not strange.
噢 是Emily
Ooh, Emily.
我听他这么对Emily说过
I heard him say that to Emily.
嘿 我以为你在家呢
Hey, I thought you were staying home.
恩 刚才在 但是和Penny说话之后
Yeah, I was, but after talking to Penny,
我明白了一些事
I realized something.
我... 首先 你俩这段感情里
I... first, she's trying much harder to stay attractive
她比你更努力地保持身材
in this relationship than you are.
第二...
And second...
我的研究没有进展可能是因为
the reason I may not be progressing in my research is
我为自己营造的环境太过于舒心了
I've created too pleasant of an environment for myself.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
根据耶基斯和多德森的经典心理实验表明
According to a classic psychological experiment
要想让一个人表现出最佳状态
by Yerkes and Dodson, in order to maximize performance,
必须营造出一种高效率焦虑状态
one must create a state of productive anxiety.
所以我希望你们都能帮我一下
So I'd like to ask you all to do something for me.
让我保持清醒
Keep me on my toes.
狠狠虐我
Just throw me off my game.
基本就是 你们用尽方法让我的生活无比悲惨
E... Essentially, go out of your way to make my life miserable.
等等
Hold on.
我们有什么好处吗?
What's in it for us?
- 我想...  - 好的 我们答应了!
- Well, I suppose...  - Okay, we'll do it!
搞定
Done.
33秒
33 seconds.
好了 那是我们的基线
Okay, that'll be our baseline.
我本不想告诉你
You know, I don't want to tell you
怎样做好自己的工作 但是一只老鼠走出迷宫后
how to do your job, but when a mouse completes a maze,
都会获得一点食物奖励
it gets a food pellet.
老鼠的大脑也会被用镊子夹出来
It also gets its brain plucked out with tweezers.
那最后一餐你就给它吃那么点食物?
And his last meal was a food pellet?
你真是个禽兽
You're a monster.
好了接下来 我们要用
All right, next, we're gonna introduce
一种焦虑诱导刺激 测量你的压力水平
an anxiety-inducing stimulus, measure your stress levels
再看看它如何影响你解决问题的效率
and see how it affects your problem-solving rate.
很好
Very well.
祝你好运... 我可是很淡定的人
And good luck... I'm a pretty laid-back guy.
准备好了?
Ready?
开始
Begin.
你为什么戳爆它?
Why'd you pop it?
抱歉 我本来是要戳你的心脏的
I'm sorry, I was aiming for your heart.
我知道你不喜欢
Look, I know you don't like it'
但是这是实验的关键
but that's the point of the experiment.
我要刺激你
I need to irritate you
才能找到你的最佳焦虑区
to find your optimal anxiety zone.
既然你说了不能挠痒痒 不能放波尔卡舞曲
And you said no to tickling, polka music
也不能看着我吃香蕉
or watching me eat a banana.
有谁是横着吃香蕉的?!
Who eats them horizontally?!
我妈说好女孩就该这么吃
My mother said that's how good girls do it.
也许这就是在浪费时间
Perhaps this was a waste of time.
嘿Sheldon
Sheldon,
你是一个卓越的科学家
you're a remarkable scientist.
耐心一点... 我保证
Just be patient... I'm sure you'll find the breakthrough
你能找到突破点
you've been looking for.
谢谢
Thank you.
而且就算你只老老实实做研究
And if you only do solid research
没有突破性发现
instead of making a groundbreaking discovery,
那又怎样呢?
what does it matter?
"老老实实做研究"?!
"Only do solid research"?!
哦... 我来找你帮忙 你却侮辱我?!
Uh... I come to you for help, and you insult me?!
我以为你至少能...
I thought the least that you would do would be...
看 你的焦虑水平达到理想值了
Look, your anxiety levels are right in the zone.
真的?
Really?
真棒啊
Oh, that's fantastic.
等等 下降了
N... Now, wait, they're dropping.
为什么会下降呢?
Why are they dropping?
因为它们升高了你很开心
Because you're happy they're elevated.
哦 真可恶!
Oh, that is infuriating!
看 看 又回来了
Ooh, look, they went back up again.
太好了
Terrific.
不 又下降了!
Oh, no, they went back down!
好了 伙计们 你们想玩什么游戏?
All right, guys, what game do you want to play?
我来看看
Let's see.
不如玩 "Emily还是Cinnamon"
How about "Emily or Cinnamon"
你不觉得这样很奇怪吗
You know what? I think it's a little weird
你总是能记住我说的话
that you remember me saying all these things.
可能是... 你嫉妒我的感情生活吧
Maybe the truth is... you're jealous of all my relationships.
可能是吧
Oh, maybe I am.
谁不想成为那个女孩
Who wouldn't want to be the girl,
也有可能是狗狗 可以听到你这么说:
or possibly dog, to hear the words:
"你真幸运
"You're so lucky.
可以拥有这一头闪亮无比的秀发"
You have the shiniest hair".
这个有点难
That is a tough one.
我...我知道他给她俩都梳过头
Uh, I...I know he brushes both of them.
- 先生们...  - 嗯
- Gentlemen...  - Yeah.
我找到了你们能刺激我的最好方案
I have figured out the perfect way for you to irritate me.
我希望你们能做我的专业挑刺员
I'd like you to be my intellectual sparring partners.
从现在起 只要我说什么
From now on, when I make an assertion,
你们就挑什么刺
I need you to challenge it.
所以无论你说什么 我们只要否定它就好了?
So you just want us to disagree with whatever you say?
是的
Yes.
- 你觉得这样能起作用?  - 是的
- And you think that's going to help?  - Yes.
但是我觉得根本没用
Well, I don't think that's gonna help at all.
会的
Oh, no, it will.
通过让我的大脑保持运转 我会更专注
See, by keeping my mind engaged, I'll become more focused.
Howard说得对... 没用的
Howard's right... that'll never work.
前提就不要在跟我争了
Stop fighting me on the premise.
这是有科学测试有效的
It's scientifically valid.
我提出观点
I'm going to advance propositions,
你们只管来质疑
I just want you to challenge me.
你肯定不希望我们这么做
I don't think that's what you want at all.
怎么会 我当然希望
Why, of course it's what I want.
如果我不希望的话 我怎么又会说我希望
Why would I say it's what I want if it's not what I want?
因为你心口不一
Because it is what you want, and it's not what you said.
我就这么点点要求 你们居然都不帮忙
I ask you for one simple thing, and you can't even do it.
- 我们可以帮啊  - 好啊 那就来吧
- Yes, we can.  - Yeah, well, then do it.
不
Nah.
你们真差劲
You guys are the worst.
谢谢 真的管用
Thank you, I think that was helpful.
季度销售冠军可以
So, whichever rep has the best sales for the quarter
获得夏威夷双人游
gets a trip for two to Hawaii.
对你和Leonard来说 太浪漫啦
That would be so romantic for you and Leonard.
显然你没有见过他
Yeah, clearly you haven't seen him on the beach
带着金属探测器在沙滩上走来走去
walking around with his metal detector.
我要是能去夏威夷
If I were going to Hawaii,
我要一整天都泡在Keck天文台
I'd spend all my time at the Keck Observatory.
你知不知道 那里的望远镜
Did you know that the telescopes there have
分辨率比哈勃还高?
better resolution than the Hubble?
真的?
Really?
你想去夏威夷吗?
Want to go to Hawaii?
女士们?
Ladies?
女士们...
Ladies...
女士们?
Ladies?
进来
Come in.
女士们
Ladies.
什么事?
What's up?
你们可能已经知道了 我在试验
As you may know, I've been experimenting
提高焦虑水平
with elevated anxiety levels,
我想
and I thought,
还有什么比参加一场
what better way to increase my discomfort
没品的未经删减的三俗谈话
than to subject myself to an evening
更好的方式呢?
of tasteless uncensored crotch talk?
你到底以为我们都聊什么?
What exactly do you think goes on here?
嗯...
Well...
你们在进行一场不适于有异性
conversations that you wouldn't be comfortable having
参与的谈话
in front of the opposite sex.
比如 谁的宫颈最好
You know, who has the best cervix.
哪种姨妈巾最风靡
Which sanitary napkin is all the rage right now.
怎么啪啪男神的屁屁
Men's buttocks, and how you want to pat and squeeze them.
我们在聊Penny的工作
We were talking about Penny's job.
她的工作有多困难?
And how difficult it is to do
她这么膨胀 暴躁 脑子抽筋
when she's bloated, cranky and crampy?
继续
Continue.
Sheldon 我们都是正常人
Sheldon, we are just people.
我们跟你们聊的东西都一样
We talk about the same things you guys talk about.
你们聊狼人可以游泳吗?
You talk about if werewolves can swim?
Leonard说可以
See, Leonard says yes,
但是我认为这决定于他被咬之前
but I say it depends on if the human could swim
是不是会游泳
before he was bitten.
你怎么看?
What do you think?
我们来聊聊大姨妈吧
Let's just talk about our periods.
不 等一下
No, hold on.
游泳是犬科动物的本能
All canines instinctively know how to swim.
狼人怎么能不会游泳?
Why wouldn't a werewolf have the same abilities?
因为他们不是完完全全的狼
Well, they're not a hundred percent wolf.
它们是狼人 半狼半人
They're a werewolf... that's only part wolf.
就像拿苹果跟橘子比
It's like comparing apples to oranges.
谢谢
Thank you.
技术层面上讲 是苹果在月圆之夜
Oh, and technically, it's apples that turn into were-oranges
变成了橘子
when the moon is full.
嗨 真有趣
Hey, this is fun.
什么时候你们不一起大姨妈综合征的时候我们再来玩
We should do it sometime when you aren't all PMS'ing.
拜拜
Bye.
怎么回事?
What is going on?
噢
Oh.
我要维持住焦虑水平
Uh, I need to keep my anxiety at the right level,
所以需要达斯・维达 小丑 和哥斯拉的吼叫声
so I'm using Darth Vader, the Joker, and Godzilla's roar
来锁定那个有效区域
to keep me in that sweet spot.
我尝试过把泰勒斯威夫特也混进去
Uh, I tried including Taylor Swift in the mix,
可没想到我这么爱她
but turns out I love her.
拜托戴耳机啊
Well, at least listen to it through headphones.
我要睡觉 晚安
I'm trying to sleep. Good night.
哎!
Boy!
泰勒是对的... 黑我的人会不停地\黑黑黑黑
Taylor was right... haters gonna hate, hate, hate, hate, hate.
你最近工作很忙嘛
You've been working so much lately,
很高兴你没有忘记约会之夜
I'm glad you didn't forget about date night.
当然
Of course.
Sheldon啊
Sheldon.
嗯
Yeah.
也许你应该把本子放下 来跟我说话
Maybe you want to put the notebook away and talk to me.
我可以双线程
I can do both.
哦不 我的大脑可是最优配置
No, my brain is working at optimal capacity.
哦不 我可以边跟你聊天
No, I can have a conversation with you
边解决暗物质质子的衰减问题
and solve the dark matter proton decay problem at the same time.
好吧 今天过得怎么样?
Fine. How was your day?
言之有理
Oh, you said it.
Sheldon啊
Sheldon.
Sheldon 我很担心你
Sheldon, I'm worried about you.
你不吃东西
You're not eating,
你几天不睡
you haven't slept in days,
而且 说实话 那帽子都臭了
and, to be honest, that cap is starting to smell.
我知道啊
I know.
他已经取代了哥斯拉 成为了我焦虑的源泉
It's replaced Godzilla as my principle source of anxiety.
现在是Emily一票 Cinnamon一票
Okay, so it's one vote Emily, one vote Cinnamon.
Penny 由你来打破僵局
Penny, you're the tiebreaker.
再说一遍
Say the quote again.
"我们都是天秤座 太好了"
"It's just so perfect that we're both Libras."
哇 好难
Wow, this is hard.
我选Cinnamon
I'm gonna say Cinnamon.
- 猜对啦!  - 耶!  - 拜托!
- Yes!  - Yes!  - Come on!
这是最后一次 我发誓
That was the last one, I promise.
再也不玩了
We won't play anymore.
谢谢
Thank you.
要知道一旦被她发现 她可是要伤心的
'Cause if she ever found out, it would hurt her feelings.
是伤Emily的心吗?
Emily's feelings?
是Emily的
Yes, Emily.
- 漂亮!  - 猜得好!
- Nice!  - Yay! Good job!
随便你们 Sheldon去哪了?
Whatever. Where's Sheldon?
去约会了
Date night.
Amy一定会觉得很无聊
Mmm, that can't be much fun for Amy.
今天上班的时候 他喝了生平第一罐红牛
You know, at work today, he tried his first Red Bull.
出什么事了?
What happened?
他绕着圈儿
He chased a squirrel
追了会儿松鼠 然后...
around the quad for a while and...
然后就在我车里吐了起来
then threw up in my car.
难道你们不觉得该劝他停下来了吗?
Don't you think you should make him stop all this?
我不知道... 他也没碍着别人
I don't know... he's not really hurting anybody.
把呕吐物从手套箱铲出来的又不是你
You didn't have to scoop vomit out of your glove compartment.
他可是完成了不少工作
He is getting a lot of work done.
还对质子衰退提出了很独到的见解
He had a pretty interesting take on proton decay.
他要是攻破这个 这可是改变了历史啊
Wow, if he cracks that, it's a game changer, guys.
它将彻底颠覆我们
It'll completely redefine our understanding
对物理世界的理解
of the physical universe.
嗯 的确会
Hmm, it would.
好了 继续"Emily"还是"Cinnamon"的游戏
Okay, back to "Emily or Cinnamon"
"一个小姑娘怎么吃得下这么一大块牛排"
"How can such a little girl eat such a big steak"
喂 Sheldon
Sheldon,
快把帽子摘了
I want you to take that cap off.
你唠叨的口气 对我保持焦虑真有帮助
That nagging tone is helping my anxiety, yeah.
但要是你能把声音放缓和十分之一
But if you could maybe just go ten percent less shrill,
那就真成了我的天籁之音
that'd really put the zip-a-Dee in my doo-dah.
不好意思 但我们说好
I'm sorry, but you know we agreed
约会夜不带工作的
not to bring work to date night.
就是这样 真是完美
There you go, perfect.
Sheldon 别闹了 我说真的
Sheldon, stop it, I'm not kidding.
把帽子摘了 把笔记本放一边
Take the cap off, and put the notebook away.
可我奋斗几个月后终于有所进展了
But after months of struggling, I'm finally making progress.
为了追求效率把自己逼疯不值得
You don't need to drive yourself crazy in order to be productive.
我有吗?
Or do I, hmm?
牛顿著"数学原理"一书时
Sir Isaac Newton wrote his Principia
还以为自己是只穿山甲嘞
while convinced he was an armadillo.
没这回事
That's not true.
亦真亦假 谁知道呢
Yeah, well, maybe it is, maybe it isn't.
我最近产生幻觉了
I have been hallucinating lately.
Sheldon 你不能再这样了
Sheldon, this has to stop.
你得去好好休息 保重身体
You need to get some sleep and take care of yourself.
Amy 我这几天的成果比我转战暗物质后
Amy, I have gotten more done in the last few days
这么久以来的还要多
than I have since I made the switch to dark matter.
如果我停下来 一切都付诸东流怎么办?
What if I stop doing this, and it all goes away?
你的想法和主意靠的是你的脑袋 不是你的焦虑
Your thoughts and ideas come from you, not from your anxiety.
也许吧
Hmm, perhaps.
但我就不摘帽子
But I'm not taking the cap off.
折磨自己是一回事
It's one thing to make yourself miserable,
折磨你周围所有人是另一回事
but you're making everyone around you miserable, too.
我最后命令你一次... 把帽子给我摘了
Now, I'm telling you for the last time... take the cap off.
哦!
Oh!
真的?
Really?
我要是不肯呢?
What if I don't?
另外 能等我吃完点心 再回答我吗?
And before you answer that, can I have my dessert?
然后她就把我赶出来了
And then she threw me out.
我可是她的正牌男友
Me, her very own boyfriend.
我做的不过是试图让人类
When all I've done is try to help humanity reach
更深入地理解我们所生活的世界
a more profound understanding of the world we live in.
是啊 女人呐...
Yeah, well, women...
你准备怎么做?
what are you gonna do?
我就知道你懂我的 亲爱的穿山甲牛顿
I knew you'd understand, Armadillo Isaac Newton.
好吧...
Okay...
到了
Here we are.
嘿
Hey.
你又是演的哪出?
What are you trying to pull?
科学院的主席又不在这
The president of science isn't in here.
你先躺下来 他稍后就到
You lie down, he'll be here in a minute.
好吧
Okay.
我还以为你在骗我呢
Hey, I thought you were trying to trick me.
现在 你也舒服舒服
Now, you just get comfortable.
不不 安逸是魔鬼
No, no, comfort is the enemy.
你知道怎样才算舒服吗?
You know what's comfortable?
拖鞋 毛毯 还有熊猫抱枕
Slippers and blankets and panda bears.
想象一下画着理查德・费曼脸的熊猫
Imagine a panda bear with Richard Feynman's face on it.
把车发动下 Leonard 到了采购海报的时间了
Warm up the car, Leonard, it's poster time.
早上再去吧
Maybe in the morning.
嗯 你先睡会儿
Yeah, you get some sleep.
不 我还不想睡... 你不能逼我睡
No, I don't want to go to sleep... you can't make me.
你说得对 我们逼不了你
You're right, we can't.
对极了 你们逼不了
Yeah, darn straight, you can't.
别想哄一个成年人入睡...
Try to tell a grown man to go to sleep...
# 猫猫软 #
# Soft kitty #
# 猫猫暖 #
# Warm kitty #
# 小小绒毛一团团 #
# Little ball of fur... #
这样没用的
That's not gonna work.
# 猫猫欢笑 猫猫睡觉 #
# Happy kitty, sleepy kitty #
# 喵 #
# Purr #
# 喵 喵 #
# Purr, purr. #
他虽然常常给人惹麻烦
You know, he can be a lot of trouble,
但我看他这么睡着
but when I see him lying here asleep like this,
心想...
I just think...
拿个枕头直接盖在他脸上该是多容易
how easy it would be to hold a pillow over his face.
哇 你看起来休息得不错
Wow, you look like you got some rest.
哦 我感觉好多了
Oh, I'm feeling much better.
而且我现在无需人为制造焦虑感
And I've also been continuing to make progress
也可以继续出成果了
without artificially raising my anxiety levels.
我一打开车里的暖气 就有呕泄物喷出来
I turned on the heat in my car and some vomit came out,
所以我的焦虑... 可不小
so my levels... right up there.
大家好
Hey, guys.
可以让Emily陪我们一起吃午饭吗?
Mind if Emily joins us for lunch?
- 好呀  - 没问题  - 当然
- Yeah, sure.   - Yeah, no problem.  - Of course not.
听说你们大家在玩个小游戏
So I hear you guys have been playing a little game.
呃 我们只是随便玩玩
Well, um, we were just kidding around.
Raj的细心温柔或许对你们来讲很好笑
Well, you may think it's funny that Raj is sweet and sensitive,
但我却觉得很性感
but I think it's sexy.
呃 为什么你嘴里有撮狗毛?
Ugh, why is there dog hair in your mouth?